

Raj Kar

Pythonista & Web Developer

About Me

Hello! I'm **Raj**, A 19 years old BCA student. Doing random stuffs, want to explore the Programming world. More passionate about BACKEND and ...More

Age

19

Email

rajkar921@gmail.com

Phone

+917001441129

Address

TelKal Para, Dist Purulia, West Bengal, INDIA

Professional Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Python

Java

C++

Work Experience

Currently at 3rd Sem at BCREC

Feb, 2021 - Present

Currently, I've not enough work experience cause I'm just in the 3rd sem of BCA.

Project Experience

Blog Website at Code-with-Raj

Dec, 2020 - Jan, 2021

Create a Personal blog website, Using Html, Css, Js, Bootstart5, and as BACKEND used Python, Flask.

Open Source Contributor at Github

Jun, 2020 - February, 2021

Contribute to a lot of Open source projects like ZTM, Nptel Projects, My Python, JS projects.

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html#contact 3/5

Education

Bachelor of Computer Application from Dr B C Roy Engineering College - Durgapur.

2019 - 2022

Currently, pursuing my Bachelor's Degree from BCREC. Currently, I'm on 3rd Sem.

Humanities and Computer from Purulia M.M High School

2007 - 2011

After Class 10, complete my 2 years of Higher Secondary from M.M High school at Arts.

Contact

Address

TelKal Para, Dist Purulia, West Bengal, INDIA

Phone

+917001441129

Email

rajkar921@gmail.com

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html#contact 5/5